* [Call Wheaton: (630) 469-7696](tel:(630)%20469-7696)

* [Call St. Charles: (630) 883-0856](tel:(630)%20883-0856)

* [Call St. Charles: (630) 883-0856](tel:(630)%20883-0856)
* [Call Wheaton: (630) 469-7696](tel:(630)%20469-7696)

Menu

* Home
* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
--------------

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DPD Smiles collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.dpdsmiles.com website (“Site”).

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. **THESE COOKIES DO NOT IN ANY WAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER.** We may at anytime use these cookies to serve relevant ads on other third party websites via Google AdWords Remarketing and AdRoll retargeting platforms. The cookies are used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Google AdWords Remarketing and AdRoll re-targeting allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.”

#### How we use collected information

DPD Smiles may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* _To run and operate our Site_  
    We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
* _To improve customer service_  
    Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
* _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
    To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* _To send periodic emails_  
    We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

DPD Smiles has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

This document was last updated on June 1st, 2020

### Do you have any quetions?

----------------------------------------------------------

* DPD Smiles is a pediatric, orthodontic and oral surgery dental office committed to creating and nurturing long lasting relationships.

---------------------------------------------

* [722 S President St,  
    Wheaton, IL 60189](https://www.google.com/maps/place/DPD+Smiles/@41.8583364,-88.0924071,15z/data=!4m6!3m5!1s0x880e5312f2393f57:0x261bef4c19881810!8m2!3d41.8583364!4d-88.0924071!16s%2Fg%2F1trprcy4?entry=ttu&g_ep=EgoyMDI0MDgyMy4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D)

* [Call: +1 (630) 469-7696](tel:+1%20(630)%20469-7696)

----------------------------------------------------

* [1203 E Main St,  
    St. Charles, IL 60174](https://www.google.com/maps/place/DPD+Smiles+-+Pediatrics+%26+Orthodontics/@41.916278,-88.3022508,15z/data=!4m6!3m5!1s0x880f03d7da9cde29:0x489ed1cf1461e5cb!8m2!3d41.916278!4d-88.3022508!16s%2Fg%2F11nmprq03n?entry=ttu&g_ep=EgoyMDI0MDgyMy4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D)

* [Call: +1 (630) 883-0856](tel:+1%20(630)%20883-0856)
